Good morning and welcome to Mario Radio.
Today we have a letter from
languishing lonesome boy.
Kai, hear me out, he writes.
My girlfriend just ghosted
me and I'm super depressed.
I think I may have scared her off
with my out of the blue proposal.
And I spent my whole paycheck on
her birthstone engagement ring too.
So you managed to get the
bow and arrow back, huh?
Yeah, I found it in Akira's apartment.
He'd been using his stand to help
himself to whatever he wanted.
It all totaled up to be 500 million
yen, and the police are already on it.
You can try using your stand if you want,
but then I'd be forced to hunt
you down and finish you off.
You can't lay a finger
on me while I'm in here!
Chili Pepper has been retired.
Even if he broke out,
I doubt he'd attack us.
Mr. Jotaro?
What about the bow and arrow?
It's going to the Speedwagon
Foundation for analysis.
If things go the way I want, we'll
unlock the mystery of stands.
Great!
That's fantastic!
After you're done, all
of this will be over!
It feels weird celebrating, but woohoo!
We cracked the case!
We're still questioning Otoishi
about the other stand users.
There's no way of knowing
how many he awakened.
You'll need to stay on your toes. Got it!
The Japanese sure know
how to make a cup of joe!
Waitress!
Refill please! Careful!
Pay attention!
I swear, you're such a klutz.
I can't turn around for one second.
Josuke, it's almost time
for the bus, isn't it?
Oh.
Uh, yeah.
I guess you're right.
Come on, get up. We gotta go.
You think those two are going to be okay?
I'm kind of worried.
Holy cannoli!
This is the yummiest
cake I've ever tasted!
Waitress, I want some more, please!
This is Tomoko.
May I ask who's speaking?
Oh, hey, Mom. It's me.
Hmm? Josuke?
This is a surprise.
You never call the house.
Are you in some kind of trouble?
No, uh, why would you think that?
Uh, anyway, you're gonna be home
for the rest of the day, right?
Yeah, that's the plan.
Is there something I should know?
No, I just wanted to make sure.
Bye!
Hey, wait!
What in the world?
I swear, that kid had better
not be up to anything fishy.
That was a close one.
I hope Mom doesn't think something's up.
This'll be hard enough
without her catching on early.
You've got to be kidding.
I told that old geezer to
wait until I was off the phone
Hey, wait up
Did you hear me?
I asked you to slow down old man
Sorry about that you weren't calling
after me were you? Forget it.
We'll never flag down
a cab at this hour so
we're gonna have to
take a bus to my house.
Oh, one more thing.
I know this sounds kind of
pushy, but it has to be said now.
Make sure you keep your distance
from mom, and no talking to her.
Before we go anywhere, you have to
promise me the terms are non-negotiable.
Because if I know my mother, a
simple visit won't be enough for her.
She'll become an emotional train wreck.
I'm well aware.
All right, then.
I promise.
and so we're clear i'm
not i'm gonna be calling
you mr joestar the
entire time you're here.
look this is awkward but i need to
be as clear as possible strangers
that's all the two of us were till
now i know that sounds kind of
harsh but it's the truth like it
or not calling you my father just
isn't something i'm willing to do
here's the deal after you see mom you
should hurry back to America.
Hmm?
Yes, you're right.
I completely understand.
Sorry to
trouble you. Shit.
I don't think this could
be any more awkward.
I know the best thing
would be to open up, but you can't
force what isn't meant to be.
Hey, Mr. Josta - Huh?
Excuse me, by any chance, did a
big grandpa-looking guy walk by?
He just got on that long-haul bus. Huh?
What the hell were you thinking?!
Sorry for the hassle.
You said we were going to
get on a bus, so I did.
And it would seem you caught
up not a minute too soon.
From the looks of things, we were
just about to merge onto the freeway.
I'm starting to think
I should have let that
damn bus take you all the way to Hokkaido!
At least then I'd -
Oh, damn stomach cramp!
I didn't mean to inconvenience you.
Hey, Josuke.
Sort of feels like something's pulling
at my pants leg. Yeah? Better be careful.
If you drop your guard, it'll drag
you off somewhere and eat you.
Huh?
Josuke!
Get over here, we've got a stand user!
Oh, yeah, you're right.
In fact, there are two users.
And for the record, I'm talking about us.
I'm really thirsty.
White a minute.
These aren't footprints.
Hands?
They're handprints!
Oh my god!
The stand just left, Josuke!
Did you hear that?
It's right there!
You can see it in the sand!
Yeah, there's no way in hell
I'm letting him meet Mom now.
Not when he's seeing and hearing things.
If it weren't for all this
dag-blasted concrete, I could find it!
Where'd it go?
It vanished!
Why did you disappear? Come back!
Great.
This old man is nothing but trouble.
Hermit Purple!
Beat it, mutt! Go on!
Shoo, shoo, get!
Hey, uh, am I crazy or is that crying?
Over here, Josuke. Hmm?
It's just a baby.
I'm holding a tiny naked baby in my hands.
I know it sounds strange,
but it's invisible. What?
It's hard to believe, but you're right.
I can feel its soft skin.
How is this even possible
a bonafide invisible baby?
From what I can tell it can't
be any older than six months!
I want to know how it turned invisible in
the first place and how to get out here?
I'm guessing it's the work of a stand but
Why on earth would an enemy
stand user turn a baby
invisible and where the
hell is this kid's mother?
Nothing about this makes any sense.
Hey, Josuke, call me crazy, but I
think the baby is the stand user. What?
Yeah, it just isn't aware
of its abilities yet.
Whenever it was separated from its mother,
the poor little thing must have turned
invisible based on pure instinct.
Duress in adults can trigger ulcers,
hair loss, and premature graying.
But in the case of this baby,
it's activated its stand powers.
If we can find its mother, I think
we might be able to solve this.
Oh, freaking great!
Well, don't just stand there
and make it stop crying!
I, uh, don't exactly know how to do that.
I have a little bit of experience with
this, but that was a long time ago.
There, there, coochie-coochie-goo.
Ah, so that's where it is.
Well, is it a boy or a girl?
Yep, this hand has never let me down.
Cairo!
Hmm...
I'm pleased to say, it's
a girl! Oh, I get it!
That's why you had to
use your hand, right?
How else could you tell?
Cairo!
There's something else
I should know about?
Josuke!
Do you have any tissues?
Huh?
Cairo!
Th-that nauseating smell!
Why the hell is it coming from your hand?
Are you saying she? Yeah!
I had no idea she'd even done it
until I got a nose full of nasty,
and I just finished scratching
my beard with his hand!
Here, I'm returning your manuscript.
I'm looking forward to the
revisions on the second draft.
Do your best.
We're stuck with her for now,
so it looks like we'll need to
pick up formula and diapers.
And since we don't want her going
au naturel, she needs some clothes.
I'm counting on you, Mr. Joestar. What?
You want me to buy everything?
Yeah, I can't go in there.
You have any idea how
that would look to people?
Somebody could walk by and
catch me buying baby stuff.
People would start to talk.
They'd see me as some stupid 16-year-old
bad boy who knocked up some poor chick.
Okay, I see your point, but I only have
American Traveler's checks at the moment.
I guess I have no choice.
Put whatever you buy on my card.
Sorry.
Stay away from all the expensive stuff.
I've worked my ass off to build
up that little nest egg, got it?
Yeah, yeah, I understand.
Welcome, my good sir.
Is there something I can
assist you with today?
Possibly.
Do you have disposable diapers here?
You bet your bonnet we do.
Is this your first time?
Hmm?
Well, yeah, I suppose it is.
These diapers are a cinch to change,
even for customers able to live
at home without assistance.
You'll rest well with these.
Uh...
no, uh, the diapers aren't for me.
They're for a baby I'm looking after.
Goodness!
I'm sorry, how rude of me.
Of course they're for a baby.
First off, would you
like traditional diapers?
Or maybe training pads.
Hmm? Beg your pardon?
As you can see,
although traditional
diapers require a cover,
they're far more economical and
less wasteful than training pads.
Well, I'm not really sure.
Can I just have this one right here?
And what size would you like?
What do you mean?
How old is the baby, sir?
Depending on your child's unique
shape, we have preemies, small,
medium, large, and extra large.
And not to worry, we have diapers for
boys and girls, so you can't go wrong.
In my day, picking these
out was a lot easier.
Let's see.
I know that she's a girl,
and when I held her,
she was about this big,
give or take an inch.
When you held her?
I'm afraid I don't follow you.
And I don't want to run the risk of you
returning ill-fitting soiled diapers.
I'm sure you can understand
the problem with that.
Yeah, completely understand.
Guess I'll grab every size you have.
In addition to that, I need baby wipes,
instant formula, and baby bottles.
Well, then you are in luck.
We carry both glass and
plastic baby bottles.
Glass bottles tend to be
scratch and odor-resistant,
but can be heavy for
a baby's arms to hold.
Plastic bottles may be light, but
they have a tendency to trap odors.
Which of the two would you like today?
Let's see.
I guess I'll take the one with...
We also carry an assortment
of shapes and designs.
We have rocket ships, racing cars, and...
Ooh, the baby can hold this one by itself.
And when you turn this one upside down,
the doll does a delightful little dance.
It's so adorable.
I really don't know, so would you mind
picking out a few and calling it a day?
But you haven't seen our nipples.
The rubber ones are soft and
supple, but they lack durability.
Silicone nipples are resilient,
but they tend to be so stiff.
This is our Cheap trainer.
There's a diaphragm valve in the nipple.
And when it's coupled with the
baby's own suckling pressure,
it regulates the flow of milk, so
the little one gets the right amount.
This is the Nuke, a brand made in Germany.
It's compressed into an oval so the nipple
can mimic the mother's natural shape.
And just as if the mother was
nursing the old-fashioned way,
the milk won't flow without
the baby's jaw movement.
Oh, I'm sure they'll do.
I trust your judgment on this stuff.
I'll take them all.
We also carry nipple openings in the
circular Y and cross-shaped varieties.
Just give me everything.
And while you're at it, I need
some baby clothes and socks, too.
Oh, before I forget,
I'll be paying by card.
Thank you very much, sir.
$136,000.
Now, what would the exchange
rate be in American dollars?
If I'm not mistaken,
you move the decimal point, or
rather, 100 yen is about 80 cents.
Well, in any case, it's all for a good
cause and it's just a bunch of baby stuff.
Really?
How expensive could a couple
of Rugrat essentials be?
What is the hold up?
He's taking forever.
We don't have all day...
Get away!
Huh?
What happened with the
girl who got proposed to?
Does no reply mean she's not
interested or mulling things over?
I can't take much more of this.
If someone from class sees me
here, it's not gonna end well.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Josuke.
Here, thanks for the loan.
Yeah, great.
Now, let's get going
while the getting's good.
Now we don't have to worry about
losing her but there's still a problem
without a face she's gonna freak
out everyone she comes in contact
with I'm way ahead of you Josuke
I picked out some makeup while I
was at that store First she needs
a dab of foundation there and there
well what do you know she's actually
pretty cute when you can see her?
Yeah, you're right.
A vision of beauty.
Good idea.
This just made finding her
mother a hell of a lot easier.
We might actually pull this off.
Consider me impressed.
Nice one, Mr. Joestar.
I'm glad I could help out.
Now then, it's time we put on
the little lady's lipstick.
A few strokes for her brows and
lashes, a little here, and...
Why am I not surprised?
Toss a bit of flattery his way
in the old man's walking on air.
With your new makeover, we can walk
around without attracting any attention.
And since we can't exactly powder your
eyes, sunglasses should do the trick.
Now she's even cuter!
Here's some milk for her.
Hmm, do you think I went
too light on the foundation?
It doesn't seem to be sticking to her.
No, that's not it! What the hell?
She's fading out!
She's gone!
And my hands went with her!
This is horrible!
She can make other things invisible!
That means no solid
object is safe from her!
What now? Mr.
Joestar, drop the baby!
Let go of it, dammit!
Hurry before she turns the rest of you!
What?
I let go, but they're still invisible!
I think she's powering up!
What are we supposed to do?
Anything that gets within
a 30 centimeter radius of
the baby is going to be
turned completely invisible.
None of this is making any sense.
She can't be trying to protect
herself with her stand.
No one could take care of her if she did.
Something else must be going on here.
It seems like the effect
is triggered by anxiety.
Stress is the culprit.
Clearly, she doesn't like to be
handled by people she doesn't know.
And if she powers up any more, then
no one will be able to get near her.
We'll end up invisible, too.
Whoa, what a weird heap of junk.
Someone better pick that up.
Oh, well, not my problem.
Someone else can do it.
Gah!
Look out!
Hey, what happened?
Somebody flicked a cigarette.
Oh, you can't see it.
What the hell are you
doing, Mr. Joestar? Huh?
Either get with the program,
old man, or get out of the way!
Oh, I didn't know.
Sorry for the trouble.
The stroller outright vanished!
And it took the ground with it!
He was right, it is stress.
The more she freaks out, the
stronger her invisibility.
the ability power gets!
Tell me I didn't just hear
the baby stroller flip over!
Are you for real?
The invisible baby just fell in the water?
Where is she?
Come on, make some noise!
I don't see any bubbles! Is she?
Josuke, is there any sign of her? Shut up!
Every single horrible
thing that's happened to me
today has been because of
this doddering old has-been.
How the hell is this
irresponsible jackass my father?
A man so careless he
abandoned my mom for 16 years.
I'll never respect a
thoughtless bastard like him.
There's no way this was
ever gonna work out.
Listen, just stay out of this.
Okay, she's gotta be
around here somewhere.
I don't care if you turn me invisible too.
Just touch me! Hurry!
Come on!
She's not here!
Damn it!
Son of a...
How am I gonna find an invisible baby?
Especially when I'm waist
deep in crystal clear water!
I'm truly sorry, Josuke.
I won't be able to hold out
long, so I have a request.
Tell your mom hello.
It'd mean the world if
you gave her my message.
After all, I'm just a
tottering old man, you know.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm giving the water
a little bit of color.
There, in the center.
Do you see it?
The blood disappears towards the middle.
That's where the baby is.
Take care of her, Josuke.
Mr. Joestar...
No regular person would even
attempt what you've just done.
Not for a stranger's kid
they'd only met that day.
You're...
Well, I just wanted to look cool for you.
Tell me, did it work?
Well, that was an experience
I'll never forget.
But hey, all's well that
ends well, I suppose.
136,000 yen?
My hard-earned money!
It's all gone!
You gray-haired dude!
I did this! Huh?
Anytime I need to see your
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taking two bits
with a crystal mind.
A magenta feeling.
Take a shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a chicken cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain!
I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly?
To the arms and the lips and the face.
To the human kind of all that I need to.
I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what hit you!
When I get to you.
Oh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you, but?
Oh, I got to find out.
Oh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you, but?
Oh, I got to find out.